Hi everyone and welcome to another video here on my channel. It's a Noir handmade try on and they launched a collection called F***ing Fabulous last autumn. Normally they have a lot of wattle pieces, this time also a few flock embroidery pieces but this collection features a lot of PVC pieces which is great and which wasn't the case in the last collections. So I decided to show you two of these PVC pieces today.
actually it's two and a half pieces because I also have these gloves but I'm
going to start with a dress and you know it's totally handy that they have
pictures on the labels showing the garment so you know how it's supposed to
look all right this is the dress it's a really nice PVC fabrics super soft and
smooth and also not too noisy and dress is really short so I can't really know
but it's a standing dress not sitting dress because otherwise it goes up and
nope too short for that but I really like the puffy sleeves here they're not
Not too puffy but you can see that you have some ruffles here which is a nice design feature.
And of course all the snaps all the way down.
Golden snaps so it gives it this nice black and gold combination which I really like personally.
So I could combine the gloves with this dress of course but I have something different in
mind.
the metal accessories because I thought hey golden snaps I have some golden accessories.
I also added a choker but I think it's too much so I'm going to take it off again.
Now it's just the belt and before every one of you is going to ask it this is self-made.
I have no link for that but I'll link the No Handmade stuff in the description text.
I do like this look. I think this kind of accessory always completes an outfit.
Because the dress is nice by itself but why not pimp it a bit. I think you can also wear a purse or something.
Maybe a golden clutch. That would be nice. Or golden shoes. Who knows.
I think this is my look here.
The second outfit of this video is going to be a catsuit in combination with the gloves.
And the catsuit is basically the same design as the dress but kind of completed so to say.
And I'm going to change.
This is the catsuit!
the gloss which I'm going to put on now. And I can tell you that the snaps go all the way around it.
So no crotch zipper but crotch snaps so to say. Which is kind of really handy to put on and get into
because you can just open all the snaps and just slide into the catsuit. Anyway the design I really
again like the sleeves as i did with the dress and i think it has a nice look with the seams here and
the body leg area so it makes a nice transition also with this decorative seam here
and now you can also see the gloves
fingerless and pretty cute.
I just paired it with my normal go-to pleaser shoes
PVC look. So this is like the complete
PVC outfit with the gloves being in PVC.
And I also have gold details and snaps.
So it's a match.
It's a really cool catsuit. I think it fits really good as well. Also here in the waist it sits really tight.
And snug. The arms are okay. The legs are really long. So hardly anything to complain. Really nothing to complain about to be honest.
So thumbs up for this catsuit and also for the dress. No Handmade makes really cool stuff.
I have other no-handmade videos, you should check them out.
Which outfit do you prefer, the dress or the catsuit?
Tell me in the comments down below and give this video a thumbs up, check out my Patreon
account and see you in the next video.
Bye!